<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-20T15:44:58-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Seattle Business Review</title><subtitle>A blog about Seattle businesses and local outstanding talent.</subtitle><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><entry><title type="html">Announcing the 2023 SBR 30 Under 30 Award Recipients</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/01/19/SBR-30u30.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Announcing the 2023 SBR 30 Under 30 Award Recipients" /><published>2023-01-19T10:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2023-01-19T10:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/01/19/SBR-30u30</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/01/19/SBR-30u30.html">&lt;p&gt;The Seattle Business Review has once again announced its annual 30 Under 30 list, recognizing the city&apos;s top young professionals and entrepreneurs in a variety of industries. These individuals, all under the age of 30, have already made significant contributions to their fields and are poised for even greater success in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The selection process for the 30 Under 30 is highly competitive, with only the most accomplished and driven young professionals making the cut. The honorees were chosen based on a combination of factors, including professional accomplishments, leadership potential, and community involvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are excited to share with you the Seattle Business Review 30 under 30 recipients for this year, who are pushing boundaries and making a difference in their respective industries. These young men and women are not only making an impact on the business world but also making a difference in their community. We are proud to recognize their achievements and look forward to seeing the great things they will accomplish in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Alexander Horn
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexander-horn-086179178&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexander is a highly skilled and experienced restaurant professional who currently serves as the manager of Bamboo Sushi, a successful sushi restaurant. With a passion for food and a keen eye for detail, Alex has established himself as a respected leader in the industry.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Austin Baker&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Austin is a highly skilled ship engineer with extensive experience in the maritime industry. He is responsible for the maintenance and repair of the ship&apos;s propulsion and power systems, as well as the overall mechanical and electrical systems on board. He is well-versed in marine engineering principles and regulations, and is able to apply this knowledge to ensure the safe and efficient operation of the ship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Caroline Overstreet&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caroline is a dedicated and experienced middle school teacher. With a passion for education and a talent for connecting with students, she is a valuable asset to her school and community. She has a proven track record of success in the classroom and is able to create an engaging and inclusive learning environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Christine Angeles
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/christine-angeles&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christine is a skilled recruiting coordinator at Amazon. With a background in human resources and a talent for organization and communication, she is dedicated to finding top talent for the company and is known for her attention to detail and great communication skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Dakota Porter&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dakota is an experienced English teacher with a passion for education and a talent for connecting with students. He has a deep understanding of English language and literature, and is able to convey complex ideas in a clear and engaging way. He is able to differentiate instruction to meet the needs of diverse learners and create an inclusive and supportive classroom environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Derek Loen
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/derek-loen&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Derek is a highly skilled and experienced manufacturing engineer at Boeing. With a background in engineering he is responsible for designing and implementing manufacturing processes for aircraft production, ensuring efficiency and quality in the assembly line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Devon Parman
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/devon-parman&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Devon is a talented financial analyst for a real estate investment firm. He has a background in finance and a strong understanding of financial modeling, market analysis and investment strategies. He is responsible for providing financial analysis and recommendations on potential real estate investments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Evan Overstreet
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/evanoverstreet&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Evan is an accomplished sales professional who currently serves as an internal wholesaler of annuities. With a proven track record of success and a deep understanding of the financial services industry, Evan is a valuable asset to the company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Garret Thomson
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/garret-thomson&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Garret is an accomplished account executive for Toast, a company that specializes in point of sale and restaurant management technology. He has a background in sales and a proven track record of success in building and maintaining relationships with clients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Jacob Hurd
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jacob-hurd&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jacob is an accomplished bank manager, with a proven track record of successfully leading teams, building relationships and driving results. He has a deep understanding of the banking industry and is well-versed in developing and implementing strategies that drive growth, improve efficiency and enhance customer satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Jacob Wright
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jacob-wright&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jacob is a skilled accounting associate for Robert Half, a professional staffing and consulting firm. He has a background in accounting and a strong understanding of financial analysis, bookkeeping and tax compliance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Jake Curtis
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jacob-curtis-151288191&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jake is a senior assurance professional at Ernst &amp; Young, a leading global accounting firm. He has a background in accounting and a strong understanding of financial reporting, internal controls and auditing standards. He is responsible for leading audit engagements for clients, ensuring compliance with accounting standards and providing recommendations for improvement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Jared Hawkins
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jared-hawkins&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jared is an experienced Operations Specialist at Slalom Consulting, where he has a proven track record of managing and optimizing business processes for clients in a variety of industries. He has a deep understanding of operations management, process improvement, and project management methodologies, and is able to apply this knowledge to drive measurable results for his clients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Jimmy Price
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jamescpricejr&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jimmy is a highly experienced professional with a proven track record in both sales and marketing demand generation and the service industry. He excels in developing and implementing strategies that drive sales and increase demand for products and services. He is skilled in using data and analytics to identify new market opportunities and create targeted marketing campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Johanna Anstensen
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/johanna-anstensen&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Johanna is a skilled Project Coordinator at Sound Transit where she is responsible for coordinating and organizing all aspects of project management, including budgeting, scheduling, and resource allocation. She excels in fostering a positive and collaborative work environment and is able to effectively communicate with all members of a project team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Kelly Smith, CISA
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kelly-smith-problem-solver&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kelly is an experienced Risk Manager at Microsoft, where he is responsible for identifying, assessing and mitigating operational risks across the organization. He has a strong background in risk management, compliance, and regulations and is able to apply this knowledge to develop and implement risk management policies and procedures that align with industry standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Kevin Bowen
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kbowent&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin is the CEO of CompassionX, a professional services firm focusing on people experience strategy. Kevin is experienced in creating content, facilitating open communities, and offering go-to-market people experience consulting services for businesses seeking to improve how they attract and retain people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Lars Berglund
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/lars-berglund-92972884&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lars is a highly skilled Civil Fluids Engineer, with expertise in designing, analyzing and managing fluid systems for civil engineering projects. He has experience working with water distribution systems, sewage and drainage systems, irrigation systems, and other fluid-related infrastructure. He is well-versed in the principles of fluid mechanics, hydraulics, and hydrology and is able to apply this knowledge to design, analyze and troubleshoot fluid systems for buildings, bridges, roads, and other civil infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Lea Hogdal
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/leahogdal&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lea is an experienced and talented Interior Designer with a keen eye for detail and a passion for creating beautiful and functional spaces. She has a deep understanding of design principles, materials, and finishes, and is able to apply this knowledge to create unique and innovative spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Maria Grady, CPA
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/maria-grady-cpa-26a3a2a7&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maria is an experienced Accounting Manager at Expedia, where she is responsible for leading and conducting financial and operational audits to ensure compliance with internal policies and procedures, as well as external regulations. She has a deep understanding of accounting, finance, and internal controls, and is able to apply this knowledge to identify and mitigate risks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Megan Gezelius
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/megangezelius&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Megan is a highly experienced Project Manager at Boeing, where she is responsible for leading and managing complex aerospace projects from conception to completion. She has a deep understanding of project management methodologies and is able to apply this knowledge to develop project plans, schedules and budgets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Parker Sommerville, PhD
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/parker-sommerville-phd-344558a0&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parker is a highly skilled Business Development Analyst at Arzeda, where he is responsible for identifying and evaluating new business opportunities and helping the company grow. He has a deep understanding of market trends, competitor activity and customer needs, and is able to apply this knowledge to develop and implement business strategies that drive growth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Phillip Thomas
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/phillip-thomas-791734176&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phillip is a highly skilled Actuarial Analyst at Premera Blue Cross, where he is responsible for analyzing and interpreting complex data to help the company make informed decisions regarding risk management and pricing of insurance products. He has a deep understanding of actuarial science and is well-versed in statistical techniques used in the insurance industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Ryan Loen
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/rloen&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ryan is an experienced Risk Manager at Microsoft, where he is responsible for creating robust risk management infrastructure and reporting systems that allow for effective identification and management of risks across the organization.  He has a strong background in risk management, compliance, and regulations and is able to apply this knowledge to develop and implement risk management policies and procedures that align with industry standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Sam Robertson&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sam is an experienced and dedicated preschool teacher with a passion for early childhood education. He has a deep understanding of child development and is able to create a nurturing and stimulating learning environment for young children. He is skilled in using a variety of teaching methods and is able to differentiate instruction to meet the needs of diverse learners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Sean Doran
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sean-doran-aa97ba125&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sean is a highly skilled Creative Director at a web3 developer platform, where he leads the creative team in developing and executing innovative and effective campaigns for clients across various industries. He has a deep understanding of web3 technology, blockchain, and decentralized systems and is able to apply this knowledge to create compelling and impactful content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Sofi Grellner&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sofi is a dedicated and skilled middle school teacher who is passionate about helping students reach their full potential. She has a thorough understanding of the curriculum and designs engaging and interactive lessons that align with state standards. Her ability to differentiate instruction to meet the needs of diverse learners and create a positive and supportive classroom environment helps her students succeed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Spencer Newland
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/spencer-newland-1b099790&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spencer is a highly skilled Program Officer for the Center for International Private Enterprise (CIPE) focusing on Middle East &amp; North Africa. He is responsible for managing and implementing programs that promote democratic governance, economic reform, and private enterprise development in the region. He has a deep understanding of the political, economic, and cultural dynamics of the Middle East &amp; North Africa, and is able to apply this knowledge to design and implement effective programs. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Willa Hevly
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/willa-hevly&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Willa is a highly skilled professional in performance measurement and evaluation at King County. She is responsible for designing, implementing and analyzing performance measurement systems to assess the effectiveness of programs and services provided by the county. She has a deep understanding of performance management principles and methodologies, and is able to apply this knowledge to develop meaningful performance metrics and evaluate program outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Yuya Era
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuyaera&quot;&gt;
              &lt;span class=&quot;fa-stack fa-sm&quot;&gt;
                &lt;i class=&quot;fab fa-linkedin 1x&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;	
              &lt;/span&gt;
 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yuya is a visual designer for Microsoft with a passion for design, a deep understanding of design principles, user experience and design software tools. He has a proven track record of success and is able to create visually stunning designs that are user-friendly and easy to navigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script data-goatcounter=&quot;https://sbr.goatcounter.com/count&quot;
        async src=&quot;//gc.zgo.at/count.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">The Seattle Business Review has once again announced its annual 30 Under 30 list, recognizing the city&apos;s top young professionals and entrepreneurs in a variety of industries. These individuals, all under the age of 30, have already made significant contributions to their fields and are poised for even greater success in the future.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Seattle Busines Recap: 2022</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/21/2022-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Seattle Busines Recap: 2022" /><published>2022-12-21T10:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2022-12-21T10:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/12/21/2022-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/21/2022-review.html">&lt;p&gt;As we look back on the past year in Seattle, it&apos;s clear that the business landscape has continued to evolve and adapt to changing circumstances. Here are some of the key trends that have shaped the business landscape in Seattle in 2022:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The continuation of remote work: The COVID-19 pandemic has had a lasting impact on the way we work, and remote work has become the norm for many businesses in Seattle. While some companies have started to bring employees back to the office, many have opted to continue with remote work arrangements, citing the benefits of increased productivity and cost savings. This trend is likely to continue into the future, with a hybrid model of remote and in-office work becoming more common.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The growth of the tech industry: The tech industry has always been a major driver of the local economy in Seattle, and this year has seen continued growth in this sector. Companies in the tech industry have benefited from the shift to remote work and the increased demand for cloud computing and other technologies that enable it. The growing use of artificial intelligence and automation in various industries has also contributed to this trend.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The rise of e-commerce: The COVID-19 pandemic has accelerated the trend towards online shopping, and businesses in Seattle that have been able to adapt to the e-commerce model have thrived. This trend is likely to continue into the future, with consumers becoming more comfortable with shopping online and businesses seeking to tap into the growing market.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The impact of the pandemic: Despite the rollout of vaccines, the COVID-19 pandemic continues to have an impact on businesses in Seattle. Many companies have had to pivot their operations or find new ways to serve customers in the face of lockdowns and other restrictions. The pandemic has also led to a rise in unemployment, with many workers in the city losing their jobs or facing reduced hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, 2022 has been a challenging year for businesses in Seattle, but it has also presented opportunities for growth and innovation. As we move into the new year, it will be important for businesses to continue to adapt and evolve in order to thrive in an ever-changing landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dont forget! Nominations for the SBR 30 under 30 awards are open until January 1st 2023. If you have a colleague deserving recognition don&apos;t hesitate to fill out the form &lt;a href=&quot;https://tlu7lbul39w.typeform.com/to/Isn9YVMn?typeform-source=seattlebusiness.review&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">As we look back on the past year in Seattle, it&apos;s clear that the business landscape has continued to evolve and adapt to changing circumstances. Here are some of the key trends that have shaped the business landscape in Seattle in 2022:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nominations are now open for the SBR 30 under 30 award!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/05/thirty-under-thirty.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nominations are now open for the SBR 30 under 30 award!" /><published>2022-12-05T19:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2022-12-05T19:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/12/05/thirty-under-thirty</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/05/thirty-under-thirty.html">&lt;p&gt;The Seattle Business Review is excited to announce that nominations are now open for our annual 30 under 30 award. This prestigious award recognizes the top 30 young professionals under the age of 30 who are making a significant impact in their industry and the local community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you know a colleague who deserves recognition for their hard work and achievements? Now is the time to nominate them for the 30 under 30 award! We are looking for individuals who are innovative, ambitious, and driven, and who are making a positive difference in their field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To nominate a colleague for the 30 under 30 award, simply visit our website and fill out the nomination form. Be sure to provide detailed information about the nominee and why they are deserving of this award. Nominations will be accepted until January 1st 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&apos;t miss this opportunity to showcase the talent and achievements of your colleagues! Nominate a deserving individual for the 30 under 30 award today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;https://tlu7lbul39w.typeform.com/to/Isn9YVMn?typeform-source=seattlebusiness.review&quot;&gt;Click here to submit a nomination for the 2023 SBR 30 under 30 award!&lt;/a&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">The Seattle Business Review is excited to announce that nominations are now open for our annual 30 under 30 award. This prestigious award recognizes the top 30 young professionals under the age of 30 who are making a significant impact in their industry and the local community.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Small Business Highlight: Project Bionic</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/11/12/project-bionic.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Small Business Highlight: Project Bionic" /><published>2022-11-12T06:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2022-11-12T06:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/12/project-bionic</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/11/12/project-bionic.html">&lt;p&gt;Project Bionic is a social media marketing company based out of the Ballard neighborhood in Seattle. Founded in 2016, the company has quickly established itself as a leader in the world of social media marketing, offering a wide range of services to help businesses and organizations increase their online presence and engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the key reasons for Project Bionic&apos;s success is its team of experienced and talented professionals. The company&apos;s founder and CEO, Josh Dirks, has over a decade of experience in the marketing industry, and has assembled a team of experts in various fields, including social media strategy, content creation, and advertising. This wealth of knowledge and expertise allows Project Bionic to provide personalized and effective solutions for its clients.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to its team, Project Bionic also prides itself on its commitment to staying up-to-date with the latest trends and developments in the world of social media. The company regularly attends industry conferences and events, and is always on the lookout for new and innovative ways to help its clients succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project Bionic offers a wide range of services to its clients, including social media strategy development, content creation, advertising management, and more. The company has worked with a diverse range of clients, including small businesses, non-profits, and large corporations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, Project Bionic is a leading social media marketing company based in the Ballard neighborhood of Seattle. With its experienced team and commitment to staying at the forefront of the industry, the company is well-positioned to help businesses and organizations succeed in the world of social media.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">Project Bionic is a social media marketing company based out of the Ballard neighborhood in Seattle. Founded in 2016, the company has quickly established itself as a leader in the world of social media marketing, offering a wide range of services to help businesses and organizations increase their online presence and engagement.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2022 Fall Small Business Trend Report</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/10/02/trends.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2022 Fall Small Business Trend Report" /><published>2022-10-02T20:45:13-07:00</published><updated>2022-10-02T20:45:13-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/10/02/trends</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/10/02/trends.html">&lt;p&gt;Seattle, known for its thriving tech industry and rainy weather, is home to a vibrant small business community. In recent years, several trends have emerged that are shaping the future of small businesses in the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest trends in Seattle&apos;s small business community is the growth of tech-focused companies. The city&apos;s proximity to major tech hubs like Silicon Valley and the abundance of talented software developers in the area have made it a hotbed for startups and small businesses in the tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;What&apos;s Next?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another trend that is gaining momentum in Seattle is the rise of socially and environmentally conscious businesses. Many small businesses in the city are embracing sustainability and corporate social responsibility, offering eco-friendly products and services and giving back to the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The growth of online commerce has also had a major impact on small businesses in Seattle. More and more customers are turning to the internet to shop, making it essential for small businesses to have an online presence. Many small businesses in the city have embraced e-commerce, either by creating their own online stores or using platforms like Amazon and Etsy to sell their products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food and beverage industry is also a major part of Seattle&apos;s small business community. The city is home to a thriving coffee scene, with many small coffee shops and roasters offering unique blends and roasts. The craft beer industry is also booming in Seattle, with a growing number of microbreweries and taprooms popping up throughout the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the small business community in Seattle is vibrant and diverse, with a wide range of companies serving the city&apos;s residents and visitors. From tech startups to environmentally conscious businesses and the thriving food and beverage industry, Seattle&apos;s small businesses are a driving force in the local economy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">Seattle, known for its thriving tech industry and rainy weather, is home to a vibrant small business community. In recent years, several trends have emerged that are shaping the future of small businesses in the city.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Small Business Highlight: Intercept Games</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/09/08/intercept-games.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Small Business Highlight: Intercept Games" /><published>2022-09-08T20:45:13-07:00</published><updated>2022-09-08T20:45:13-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/09/08/intercept-games</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/09/08/intercept-games.html">&lt;p&gt;Intercept Games is a Seattle-based company that has made a big splash in the gaming world with their hit indie game, &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2011 by a team of experienced game developers, Intercept Games set out to create a space exploration game that was both challenging and fun. After several years of development, &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot; was released to critical acclaim, receiving numerous awards and accolades for its innovative gameplay and realistic physics engine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot; tasks players with building and launching their own spacecraft, navigating the dangers of space and completing a variety of missions. The game offers a high degree of realism, with players having to consider factors such as fuel consumption, aerodynamics, and gravitational forces in order to successfully complete their missions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite its complex gameplay, &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot; has been a commercial success, with a dedicated fan base and a steady stream of updates and expansions. In addition to its popularity among gamers, the game has also been used by NASA and other space agencies as a training and educational tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intercept Games continues to operate out of its Seattle headquarters, working on new projects and updates for &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot; as well as other upcoming games. The company&apos;s success is a testament to the thriving indie game development scene in Seattle, and a reminder of the city&apos;s reputation as a hub for innovation and creativity.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">Intercept Games is a Seattle-based company that has made a big splash in the gaming world with their hit indie game, &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot;.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Small Business Highlight: Xealth</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/07/27/xealth.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Small Business Highlight: Xealth" /><published>2022-07-27T20:45:13-07:00</published><updated>2022-07-27T20:45:13-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/07/27/xealth</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/07/27/xealth.html">&lt;p&gt;Seattle startup, Xealth, is making waves in the digital health industry with its innovative platform for organizing and deploying digital health tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2016 by a team of experienced healthcare and technology professionals, Xealth has developed a comprehensive platform that enables health systems to easily integrate and activate digital health tools. The platform is designed to help health systems improve patient outcomes, reduce costs, and streamline operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xealth&apos;s platform is unique in its ability to support a wide range of digital health tools, including apps, devices, and services. This allows health systems to easily select and deploy the tools that are most relevant to their patients and clinical needs. In addition, the platform provides robust analytics and reporting capabilities, allowing health systems to track the effectiveness of their digital health initiatives and make data-driven decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company has already partnered with several major health systems, including Providence St. Joseph Health and the Mayo Clinic. These partnerships have demonstrated the effectiveness of Xealth&apos;s platform in improving patient outcomes and reducing costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xealth is continuing to expand its operations, with plans to develop new features and integrations for its platform. The company&apos;s success is a testament to the growing importance of digital health solutions and the need for effective platforms to support their deployment and activation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">Seattle startup, Xealth, is making waves in the digital health industry with its innovative platform for organizing and deploying digital health tools.</summary></entry></feed>