<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-19T11:41:50-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Seattle Business Review</title><subtitle>A blog about Seattle businesses and local outstanding talent.</subtitle><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><entry><title type="html">Seattle Busines Recap: 2022</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/21/2022-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Seattle Busines Recap: 2022" /><published>2022-12-21T10:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2022-12-21T10:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/12/21/2022-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/21/2022-review.html">&lt;p&gt;As we look back on the past year in Seattle, it&apos;s clear that the business landscape has continued to evolve and adapt to changing circumstances. Here are some of the key trends that have shaped the business landscape in Seattle in 2022:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The continuation of remote work: The COVID-19 pandemic has had a lasting impact on the way we work, and remote work has become the norm for many businesses in Seattle. While some companies have started to bring employees back to the office, many have opted to continue with remote work arrangements, citing the benefits of increased productivity and cost savings. This trend is likely to continue into the future, with a hybrid model of remote and in-office work becoming more common.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The growth of the tech industry: The tech industry has always been a major driver of the local economy in Seattle, and this year has seen continued growth in this sector. Companies in the tech industry have benefited from the shift to remote work and the increased demand for cloud computing and other technologies that enable it. The growing use of artificial intelligence and automation in various industries has also contributed to this trend.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The rise of e-commerce: The COVID-19 pandemic has accelerated the trend towards online shopping, and businesses in Seattle that have been able to adapt to the e-commerce model have thrived. This trend is likely to continue into the future, with consumers becoming more comfortable with shopping online and businesses seeking to tap into the growing market.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The impact of the pandemic: Despite the rollout of vaccines, the COVID-19 pandemic continues to have an impact on businesses in Seattle. Many companies have had to pivot their operations or find new ways to serve customers in the face of lockdowns and other restrictions. The pandemic has also led to a rise in unemployment, with many workers in the city losing their jobs or facing reduced hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, 2022 has been a challenging year for businesses in Seattle, but it has also presented opportunities for growth and innovation. As we move into the new year, it will be important for businesses to continue to adapt and evolve in order to thrive in an ever-changing landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dont forget! Nominations for the SBR 30 under 30 awards are open until January 1st 2023. If you have a colleague deserving recognition don&apos;t hesitate to fill out the form &lt;a href=&quot;https://tlu7lbul39w.typeform.com/to/Isn9YVMn?typeform-source=seattlebusiness.review&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">As we look back on the past year in Seattle, it&apos;s clear that the business landscape has continued to evolve and adapt to changing circumstances. Here are some of the key trends that have shaped the business landscape in Seattle in 2022:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nominations are now open for the SBR 30 under 30 award!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/05/thirty-under-thirty.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nominations are now open for the SBR 30 under 30 award!" /><published>2022-12-05T19:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2022-12-05T19:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/12/05/thirty-under-thirty</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/05/thirty-under-thirty.html">&lt;p&gt;The Seattle Business Review is excited to announce that nominations are now open for our annual 30 under 30 award. This prestigious award recognizes the top 30 young professionals under the age of 30 who are making a significant impact in their industry and the local community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you know a colleague who deserves recognition for their hard work and achievements? Now is the time to nominate them for the 30 under 30 award! We are looking for individuals who are innovative, ambitious, and driven, and who are making a positive difference in their field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To nominate a colleague for the 30 under 30 award, simply visit our website and fill out the nomination form. Be sure to provide detailed information about the nominee and why they are deserving of this award. Nominations will be accepted until January 1st 2023.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&apos;t miss this opportunity to showcase the talent and achievements of your colleagues! Nominate a deserving individual for the 30 under 30 award today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;https://tlu7lbul39w.typeform.com/to/Isn9YVMn?typeform-source=seattlebusiness.review&quot;&gt;Click here to submit a nomination for the 2023 SBR 30 under 30 award!&lt;/a&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">The Seattle Business Review is excited to announce that nominations are now open for our annual 30 under 30 award. This prestigious award recognizes the top 30 young professionals under the age of 30 who are making a significant impact in their industry and the local community.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Small Business Highlight: Project Bionic</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/11/12/project-bionic.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Small Business Highlight: Project Bionic" /><published>2022-11-12T06:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2022-11-12T06:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/11/12/project-bionic</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/11/12/project-bionic.html">&lt;p&gt;Project Bionic is a social media marketing company based out of the Ballard neighborhood in Seattle. Founded in 2016, the company has quickly established itself as a leader in the world of social media marketing, offering a wide range of services to help businesses and organizations increase their online presence and engagement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the key reasons for Project Bionic&apos;s success is its team of experienced and talented professionals. The company&apos;s founder and CEO, Josh Dirks, has over a decade of experience in the marketing industry, and has assembled a team of experts in various fields, including social media strategy, content creation, and advertising. This wealth of knowledge and expertise allows Project Bionic to provide personalized and effective solutions for its clients.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to its team, Project Bionic also prides itself on its commitment to staying up-to-date with the latest trends and developments in the world of social media. The company regularly attends industry conferences and events, and is always on the lookout for new and innovative ways to help its clients succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project Bionic offers a wide range of services to its clients, including social media strategy development, content creation, advertising management, and more. The company has worked with a diverse range of clients, including small businesses, non-profits, and large corporations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, Project Bionic is a leading social media marketing company based in the Ballard neighborhood of Seattle. With its experienced team and commitment to staying at the forefront of the industry, the company is well-positioned to help businesses and organizations succeed in the world of social media.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">Project Bionic is a social media marketing company based out of the Ballard neighborhood in Seattle. Founded in 2016, the company has quickly established itself as a leader in the world of social media marketing, offering a wide range of services to help businesses and organizations increase their online presence and engagement.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2022 Fall Small Business Trend Report</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/10/02/trends.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2022 Fall Small Business Trend Report" /><published>2022-10-02T20:45:13-07:00</published><updated>2022-10-02T20:45:13-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/10/02/trends</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/10/02/trends.html">&lt;p&gt;Seattle, known for its thriving tech industry and rainy weather, is home to a vibrant small business community. In recent years, several trends have emerged that are shaping the future of small businesses in the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest trends in Seattle&apos;s small business community is the growth of tech-focused companies. The city&apos;s proximity to major tech hubs like Silicon Valley and the abundance of talented software developers in the area have made it a hotbed for startups and small businesses in the tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;What&apos;s Next?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another trend that is gaining momentum in Seattle is the rise of socially and environmentally conscious businesses. Many small businesses in the city are embracing sustainability and corporate social responsibility, offering eco-friendly products and services and giving back to the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The growth of online commerce has also had a major impact on small businesses in Seattle. More and more customers are turning to the internet to shop, making it essential for small businesses to have an online presence. Many small businesses in the city have embraced e-commerce, either by creating their own online stores or using platforms like Amazon and Etsy to sell their products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food and beverage industry is also a major part of Seattle&apos;s small business community. The city is home to a thriving coffee scene, with many small coffee shops and roasters offering unique blends and roasts. The craft beer industry is also booming in Seattle, with a growing number of microbreweries and taprooms popping up throughout the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the small business community in Seattle is vibrant and diverse, with a wide range of companies serving the city&apos;s residents and visitors. From tech startups to environmentally conscious businesses and the thriving food and beverage industry, Seattle&apos;s small businesses are a driving force in the local economy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">Seattle, known for its thriving tech industry and rainy weather, is home to a vibrant small business community. In recent years, several trends have emerged that are shaping the future of small businesses in the city.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Small Business Highlight: Intercept Games</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/09/08/intercept-games.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Small Business Highlight: Intercept Games" /><published>2022-09-08T20:45:13-07:00</published><updated>2022-09-08T20:45:13-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/09/08/intercept-games</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/09/08/intercept-games.html">&lt;p&gt;Intercept Games is a Seattle-based company that has made a big splash in the gaming world with their hit indie game, &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2011 by a team of experienced game developers, Intercept Games set out to create a space exploration game that was both challenging and fun. After several years of development, &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot; was released to critical acclaim, receiving numerous awards and accolades for its innovative gameplay and realistic physics engine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot; tasks players with building and launching their own spacecraft, navigating the dangers of space and completing a variety of missions. The game offers a high degree of realism, with players having to consider factors such as fuel consumption, aerodynamics, and gravitational forces in order to successfully complete their missions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite its complex gameplay, &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot; has been a commercial success, with a dedicated fan base and a steady stream of updates and expansions. In addition to its popularity among gamers, the game has also been used by NASA and other space agencies as a training and educational tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intercept Games continues to operate out of its Seattle headquarters, working on new projects and updates for &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot; as well as other upcoming games. The company&apos;s success is a testament to the thriving indie game development scene in Seattle, and a reminder of the city&apos;s reputation as a hub for innovation and creativity.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">Intercept Games is a Seattle-based company that has made a big splash in the gaming world with their hit indie game, &quot;Kerbal Space Program&quot;.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Small Business Highlight: Xealth</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/07/27/xealth.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Small Business Highlight: Xealth" /><published>2022-07-27T20:45:13-07:00</published><updated>2022-07-27T20:45:13-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/07/27/xealth</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/07/27/xealth.html">&lt;p&gt;Seattle startup, Xealth, is making waves in the digital health industry with its innovative platform for organizing and deploying digital health tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2016 by a team of experienced healthcare and technology professionals, Xealth has developed a comprehensive platform that enables health systems to easily integrate and activate digital health tools. The platform is designed to help health systems improve patient outcomes, reduce costs, and streamline operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xealth&apos;s platform is unique in its ability to support a wide range of digital health tools, including apps, devices, and services. This allows health systems to easily select and deploy the tools that are most relevant to their patients and clinical needs. In addition, the platform provides robust analytics and reporting capabilities, allowing health systems to track the effectiveness of their digital health initiatives and make data-driven decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company has already partnered with several major health systems, including Providence St. Joseph Health and the Mayo Clinic. These partnerships have demonstrated the effectiveness of Xealth&apos;s platform in improving patient outcomes and reducing costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xealth is continuing to expand its operations, with plans to develop new features and integrations for its platform. The company&apos;s success is a testament to the growing importance of digital health solutions and the need for effective platforms to support their deployment and activation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Seattle Business Review</name></author><summary type="html">Seattle startup, Xealth, is making waves in the digital health industry with its innovative platform for organizing and deploying digital health tools.</summary></entry></feed>